Inventory of the Harrison Holt Riddleberger Papers 1874-1902
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Letters, 1874-1893, n.d. (Box 1-2, Folder 1-29)
  - Letters, 1884., 15 items. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - C. L. Broadus, Linden, W.Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Nov. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Wm. Lilly, Mauch Chunk, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 18 Dec. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - A. B. Brumbaugh, Huntington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 19 Dec. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - E. B. Jeffress, So. Boston, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 19 Dec. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - W. E. Craig, Staunton, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 20 Dec. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Talcott Williams, Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 22 Dec. 1884., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Letters, 1885., 108 items. (Box 2, Folder 16-23)
    - Jas. F. O'Neill, Pgh. Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Items concern speech made by H.H. Riddleberger.
    - Wm. Lamb, Norfolk, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 10 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - A. B. Cropley, Georgetown, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Thos. J. Walsh, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 26 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - [Square] N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 26 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - John W. Keogh to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 26 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Michael J. Costello, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - John W. Biddle, Baltimore, to H.H R, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - John Franey, Buffalo, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Jas. W. O'Brien, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Manus O'Connor, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Geo. B. Evans, St. Paul, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. TLS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - John W. Goff, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - [Anti-Dynamiter], Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - A. Richardson, Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Job. Hawhurst, Fairfax C.H., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Jeremiah Casey, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - J. N. Williams, Lexington, Ky., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Wm. A. A. Carsey, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Eliz. A. Meriwether, St. Louis, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Dennis Short, Brooklyn, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Edward Burke, Staunton, Va., Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Richard Murphy to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Edw. Thorne, New Brighton, S.I., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - James Leonard, Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Edward Sweeney, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - D. M. Cenoweth, Mexico, Mo., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - W. H. Barton, Mexico, Mo., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [?], Pgh.,Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Peter Daly, Northcute, Minn,, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [Philadelphia], Pennsylvania, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Wm. A. Ashby, Spotsylvania C.H., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [Pat +], Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [?], Providence, R. I., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mary Sullivan, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - C. B. Langley, Norfolk, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - W. E. Keating, Albany, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Geo. Vaubliet, Brookville, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - W. Hopkins, Glenwood, Ill., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - R. D. Sullivan, San Francisco, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - [Irish Americans], Conshocken, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - John J. McGarvey, Hazleton, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Jas. B. McGarvey, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Robt. E. Ford, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - M. A. Manning, Talcott, W. Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - P.C. O Connor, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - John F. Finerty, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Thos. O'Reilly, M.D. et al, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 Jan. 1885., 1 item. LS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - M. D. Gallagher, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Jas. R. Hodges, Texarkana, Ark., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - T. J. Corkery, Toledo, Ohio., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - [An Irish American], Lynchburg, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Wm. F. Barry, Springfield, Mass., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - John B. O Donnell, Northampton, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Thos. E. Ballard, Richmond, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Maria Artley, St. Louis, Mo., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Wm. D. Coleman, Danville, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - M.M. McGuire, Honey Creek P.O., Ill., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Jas. Hughes, So. Boston, Mass., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 31 Jan. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Fred T. Bartly, Flounce [?], to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - W. B. Barnes, Davenport, Iowa, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 1 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Timothy Crean, Chicago, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Rev. John Johnston, Petersburg, W. Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - S. T. Brockbank, Clearfield, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Jno. D. Mulhane, Steubenville, Ohio, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - [A friend], Washington, D.C., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - C.J.W. Summers, Alexandria, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Wm. Townes, Cuscowilla, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 3 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Jas. J. Martin, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 3 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - W. H. Cosby, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 4 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Irish Nationalists of Richmond, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 4 Feb. 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Committee P.O.O.H.], Philadelphia, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 4 Feb. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Jerh. B. Murphy, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Hiram Maine, Harlan, Ind., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - [Justice], Portland, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 8 Feb. 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Denis Walsh, Burlington, Vt., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 10 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence P. Boyle, Chicago, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 10 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - A. C. Heaton, Newark, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 11 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - J. H. Stapleton, Tulare, Cal., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - M. B. Holmes, Jersey City, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - John S. Byrd, Pastoria, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - S. L. Brooks, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 13 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Alex. Sloan, Lock Haven, Pa., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Wm. D. Farren, San Francisco, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Geo. Hall, Staunton, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 18 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - J. D. Hagarty, Chicago, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 18 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - J. Allen Evans, Greeley, Col., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 19 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Frank P. Hughes, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 25 Feb. 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - L.M. Olden, Jerome, Ariz., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Reuben Carroll, Wash., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Nicholas Lynch, Brooklyn, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - [?], Chicago, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 March 1885., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - [Republican American], N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Justus Schwab, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - J. J. Quantz, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - John Bryan, Canton, Ohio, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Patrick Ford, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 March 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - M. L. Gannon, Chicago, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 March 1885., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Patrick Cuddihy, Milford, Mass., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 7 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - B.L.D. Guffy, Morgantown, Ky., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 7 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Rev. P. A. McKenna, Hudson, Mass., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 9 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - P. S. Cassidy, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 11 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Frank Hume, Washington, D.C., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 14 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - P. S. Cassidy, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - J. C, Berdell, Harrisburg, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - J. J. Shiel, Little Rock, Ark., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 22 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Patrick Martin, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 25 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - A. D. Shepard, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 28 March 1885., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Geo. Steele to Thomas F. Bayard. Sec. of State, 28 April 1885., 1 item. ALCy. (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - T. F. Bayard, Washington, to George Steele, Gloucester, Mass., 2 May 1885., 1 item. ALCy. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Letters, 1886., 22 items. (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
    - Patrick Ford, N.Y. to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 1 Jan. 1886., 1 item. Facsimile. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Jos. Atkinson, Newark, N.J., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 Feb. 1886., 1 item. Printed note with ms note. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - [An Old District Man], Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 March 1886., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - John Goode, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 29 March 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - John Goode, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 March 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - H.C. Parsons, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 2 April 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - H.H. Riddleberger, Washington, to H.C. Tinsley, 3 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - P.G. Schutt, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Arthur B. Cropley, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - John Goode, Washington, D.C., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - [Anonymous], Norfolk, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 21 May 1886., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - John W. Daniel, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - T.J. Porter, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Wm. H. Tenney, Georgetown, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 26 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - H.H. Riddleberger, Washington, to Ben W. Austin, 30 May 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Item concerns the Henry C. Hoar Memorial Fund.
    - John Goode, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 14 June 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - John Power, Escanaba, Mich., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 8 July 1886., 1 item. L. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - H.W. Stamper, Richmond, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 9 July 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Fitz-John Porter, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 10 July 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - J. Mc. Perkins, Boston, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 11 July 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Alfred A. Green, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 12 July 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Felix Agnus, Baltimore, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 8 Oct. 1886., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Letters, 1887., 6 items. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - A.W. Greely, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 19 Feb. 1887., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - James P. Cooper, Richmond, Public notice, 1 April 1887., 1 item. CTy. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Alice Alfriend, assignment, 25 May 1887., 1 item. TS. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - J.G. Newman, Luray, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 20 Aug. 1887., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - M.T. Burns, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 Nov. 1887., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - M.F. Richardson, Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 21 Nov. 1887., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Letters, 1888., 14 items. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Chas. F. Button, Lynchburg, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 13 Jan. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - J.E. Jones, Macon, Ga., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 Jan. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Geo. Booker, Fort Monroe, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 18 Jan. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - C.C. Buckner, Island View, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 Jan. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - James R. Jordan, Newbern, Va., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Jan. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Jos. R. Anderson, Richmond, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 7 Feb. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - [F K. ?] [note and clipping] to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 14 March 1888., 1 item. AL. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Wm. H.S. Burgwyn, Henderson, N.C., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 30 March 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - W.S. Cappeller, Columbus, Ohio, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 16 Aug. 1888., 1 item. TLS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - James J. Rogers, Brooklyn, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 18 Aug. 1888., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Patrick Ford, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 7 Nov. 1888., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - [?], N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 8 Nov. 1888., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Patrick Ford, N.Y., to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 17 Nov. 1888., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - F. W. Hamilton, Deadwood, Dakota, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 19 Nov. 1888., 1 item. Printed. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Letters, 1889., 7 items. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Order of Hibernians, New Orleans, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 27 Feb. 1889., 1 item. Ms. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Washington, to W. H. H. Mille, 16 May 1889., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - F. H. Alfriend, Washington, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 24 Oct. 1889., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - H. W. Grady, Atlanta, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 Nov. 1889., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - W. H. Woodlin, Richmond, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 6 Nov. 1889., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Woodstock, Va. to Dr. P. McCahey, Philadelphia, 30 Nov. 1889., 1 item. Draft. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Peter McCahey, Philadelphia, to Harrison Holt Riddleberger, 5 Dec. 1889., 1 item. TLS. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Letters, 1890., 2 items. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Levi P. Morton, Washington, to J.H. Williams, 25 Jan. 1890., 1 item. Telegram. (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Item concerns the death of Harrison Holt Riddleberger.
    - Lemuel Borden, Woodstock, to Frank Riddleberger, 28 March 1890., 1 item. ALS. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Letters, 1893., 1 item. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - John W. Daniel, Lynchburg, to Emma V. Riddleberger, Woodstock, 23 May 1893., 1 item. TLS. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Letters, n.d., 27 items. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Sub-series contains letters, memos, and drafts including a number of William Mahone letters.
  Series 2: Miscellaneous Material
- Miscellaneous Material (Box 3)
  - Clippings, 1871-1888, n.d., 65 items. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Speeches and Complimentary Notes, 1880's., 27 items. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Virginia School Report, 1884., 1 item. (Box 3)
  - Southern Historical Society Papers, Vol.XXX, Richmond, Va., 1902., 376 pp. (Box 3)
  - Packet of 3"x5" cards. (Box 3)
    Cards used while papers were on deposit at Duke University.
  - Badges, 1885-1886., 2 items. (Box 3)
    - Badge, 1885., 1 item. (Box 3)
      Badge described as gold on blue silk, with inscription reading "Inauguration 1885 Reception Committee".
    - Badge, 1886., 1 item. (Box 3)
      Badge described as gold on green silk, with inscription reading "I.N. League Bazaar 1886 Chairman, Committee of Arrangements".
  - Printed Material., 10 items. (Box 3)
    - The Acme Haversack of patriotism and song, Syracuse, N.Y., Vol. 7 No.1., January 1893., 1 item. 80 pp. (Box 3)
      Item describes the account of four Civil War battles - Chancellorsville, Fredericksburg, the Wilderness, and Spottsylvania.
    - Some thoughts on the Chamberlain - Bayard treaty, n.d., 1 item. 29 pp. (Box 3)
    - Response of A. C. Braxton of Staunton, Va. to a toast to "George Washington" at the banquet of the New York Southern Society on the night of Feb. 21, 1903, 1903., 1 item. 22 (Box 3)
    - The Funding bill of 1871; the Barbour bill; the McCulloch bill, n.d., 1 item. 16 pp. Interleaved blank pages. (Box 3)
    - Message from the President of the United States transmitting a convention between the U.S. and Britain ---Grover Cleveland, July 8, 1886., 1 item. 6 pp. (Box 3)
      Item concerns the extradition of persons charged with crime.
    - The British extradition Treaty. A defective and unsafe international compact, 1889., 1 item. 4 pp. (Box 3)
      Item was signed P. McCahey, M.D., Philadelphia, Jan. 21, 1889.
    - Message of the President of the United States transmitting a convention for the extradition of criminals-, between the U.S. and Japan, 1886., 1 item. 4 pp. (Box 3)
      Item was signed signed at Tokyo, on the 29th April 1886.
    - Fishery Treaty Straws, n.d., 1 item. 11 pp. (Box 3)
      Item includes quotes of newspapers opposed to fishery treaty with Britain
    - Second Re-union of Mahone's Brigade, held on the anniversary of the Battle of the Crater, in the Opera House, Norfolk, July 31, 1876, 1876., 1 item. 13 pp. (Box 3)
      Item was printed at the Landmark book and job office, Norfolk, Va. 1876, and signed on the cover by T.A. Williams
    - Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia, at Staunton, Va. Record No. 612., 1887., 1 item. (Box 3)
      Harrison Holt Riddleberger and wife, appellants, against E. D. Newman, et als. Valley Virginian Power Press, Staunton, Va.
  Harrison Holt Riddleberger Addition, 2003.60
- Harrison Holt Riddleberger Addition
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger 1872 March 19. (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. 1874 December 10. (Box-folder 4:1)
    Three hour visit from Gov. Walker. Poverty requires rigid economy. Hailstorm relief bill. Church property at Columbia furnace.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Orkney Springs, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. [1880]. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Asks her to tell Mrs. John [Keller?] to send his code of '73 to him immediately.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. [1880]. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Senate letterhead. Passed the debt bill and reported it to the House. Meets with Gen. Bolling, who sends historical gun to Riddleberger's residence in Va.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Petersburg, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. [1880]. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Missed traveling connection and is 200 miles from where he ought to be. Friends are insisting that he give a speech.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. 1880 January 9. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Senate letterhead. Gen. M. [General Mahone]. enjoyed his time and sends his thanks.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. 1880 January 13. (Box-folder 4:2)
    Senate letterhead. Meets a 13 year old girl from South Carolina who is canvassing for the Hurricane.
  - Harrison Holt Riddleberger, Richmond, Va. to wife Emma Belew Riddleberger. 1880 January 18. (Box-folder 4:2)